creative-weblogging.com 2005-12-10

# Creative Weblogging - "Serving great bloggers" - Are you at Syndicate?

Creative Weblogging is strongly committed to protect your privacy while you interact with our content. We want to provide a safe and secure environment for you. 

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what kind and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have. 

**Collection of information**   
Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not. 

Creative Weblogging mostly collects anonymous information. For instance, we may collect information to tell us that five thousand people visit this Privacy Policy today, but we do not know their names, where they live or their date of birth - they are 'anonymous' to us. If you sign up for any of our newsletter services we only collect your email address as the only personal information. 

**Use of anonymous information**   
Creative Weblogging automatically gathers anonymous information to monitor the use of our platform like the numbers and frequency of visitors to Creative Weblogging sites and its areas, very much like television ratings that tell the networks how many people tuned in to a program. We only use such data in an aggregate way. This collective data helps us determine how much our audiences use parts of the site, so we can improve our services. Creative Weblogging may publish or provide this aggregate data to other people. 

**Use of personal information**   
Creative Weblogging will only use the personal information you have chosen to provide us for the purpose for which you provided it. Creative Weblogging will not use it for any other purpose without your consent. 

**Cookies/Third Parties**   
From time to time, Creative Weblogging or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. 

Creative Weblogging does not use Cookies but some of our advertisers do to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. Our advertisers may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you see on our site. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Site and other Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 

**No sale of personal information**   
Under no circumstances will Creative Weblogging sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information. 

**Complaints about privacy**   
If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our websites, please notify us at [mail@creative-weblogging.com](mailto:mail@creative-weblogging.com "mail@creative-weblogging.com"). 

Tags:  **Related Entries:**  
[Generate a Privacy Policy for a Site](http://www.java-entrepreneur.com/50226711/generate_a_privacy_policy_for_a_site.php "Generate a Privacy Policy for a Site")... - _Nov 25, 2005_  
[Google Privacy Policy Updated](http://www.philoneist.com/50226711/google_privacy_policy_updated.php "Google Privacy Policy Updated")... - _Oct 18, 2005_  
[Just How Many Consumers Care About Privacy Issues?](http://www.rfid-weblog.com/50226711/just_how_many_consumers_care_about_privacy_issues.php "Just How Many Consumers Care About Privacy Issues?")... - _Sep 09, 2004_  
[Privacy is Stupid](http://www.mobile-weblog.com/50226711/privacy_is_stupid.php "Privacy is Stupid")... - _Nov 17, 2004_

###### Vote for [privacy policy](http://www.creative-weblogging.com/50226711/privacy_policy.php "privacy policy") now:

###### Comment on [privacy policy:](http://www.creative-weblogging.com/50226711/privacy_policy.php "privacy policy")

[  
](http://www.creative-weblogging.com/50226711/privacy_policy.php "privacy policy")[](http://www.creative-weblogging.com/50226711/privacy_policy.php "Comments")

###### Tell a friend about [privacy policy](http://www.creative-weblogging.com/50226711/privacy_policy.php "privacy policy"):
